computeraudiophile.com 2012-12-29

# Computer Audiophile - Privacy Statement

 **Computer Audiophile Privacy Statement**

Audiophile Style, LLC is strongly committed to protecting your privacy and providing a safe online experience for all of our users and subscribers while offering the highest quality publications and services to them. This Privacy Statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, to whom we disclose personal information and other information you have provided, and how to correct or change personal information that you have provided to us. This Privacy Statement applies to Audiophile Style, LLC, subsidiaries, and affiliates. We urge you to read the complete Privacy Statement set forth below, as well as our Terms and Conditions of Use, and contact us if you have any questions. 

  I. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU?

Personal Information. We collect personally identifiable information, such as names, mailing addresses, e-mail addresses, demographic information, and similar information in a variety of situations when you register at our web site, when you enter personal information on our web site as a condition of participating in contests, promotions, or sweepstakes offered or when you wish to have a product or service fulfilled by a fulfillment partner who can meet the continuing needs of our customers.  
Our site may collect credit card and related financial information if you wish to purchase a product or subscribe to any publication or service offered. If you wish to subscribe to one of our publications or place an order for products or services online, you must generally establish a credit card account with us or our vendors.   
Information Collected Automatically. Our web sites automatically collect certain information, such as your IP address, browser type, domain name, access times and referring website address. This helps facilitate your online experience at our web sites. See Sections IV and V of this Privacy Statement for more detail on cookies, web beacons, and other information collected automatically for research and marketing purposes by our Audiophile Style, LLC. 

  II. WHAT DO WE DO WITH COLLECTED INFORMATION?

We use the personal information you provide to operate our business. A user may, at any time, opt out of receiving e-mail. We also use collected information to evaluate and administer our products and services, respond to any problems that may arise, such as web site failures, difficulties in navigating our site or accessing certain features, as well as to gauge user trends to determine what products and services are most popular with users. We allow users of our website to send articles or links by e-mail to other parties who may be interested in them. We do not retain any e-mail addresses of either the sender or recipient of such articles or links after they are sent, and do not share "send a friend" e-mail addresses with third parties. 

  III. HOW DO WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We share your personal information only as described below.  
Public Postings. You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose information, personal or otherwise, online in any community area (whether through Audiophile Style, LLC.s web site or any other service available online), that information can be collected and used by others. Accordingly, you should use caution when sharing any personal information with others in any community area (whether through Audiophile Style's web site or any other service available online).  
Required Disclosures of Information. We reserve the right to use or disclose any information without notice or consent as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request; to conduct investigations of consumer complaints or possible breaches of law; to protect the integrity of our site and our property and assure adherence to our terms of use; to protect the safety of our visitors or others; to fulfill your requests; or to cooperate in any legal investigation or process.  
Changes in Corporate Structure. In developing our business, we might sell certain assets, or the company, or parts of it, may be sold, merged or otherwise transferred. In such transactions, user information, whether personally identifiable or otherwise, may be one of the transferred assets. 

  IV. HOW DO WE USE COOKIES?

Your Web browser offers "cookies" which, if you allow their use, store small amounts of data on your computer when you visit a web site. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you and therefore cannot be used to identify you personally. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features you like best, and also enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser and our websites are viewable even if you disable the cookie function on your browser. However, if you disable cookies, some advanced and customized features or offerings will not be available to you. 

  V. HOW DO WE USE WEB BEACONS, WEB ANALYTICS, AND OTHER BEHAVIORAL MARKETING TECHNOLOGIES?

A number of technologies exist to assess consumer behavior both on-line and off-line. Audiophile Style, LLC employs a variety of these technologies, including web analytics techniques, to assess consumer behavior and to understand how we can better serve our customers. In the course of using these technologies, we automatically collect non-personal information from you, including but not limited to the following types of information: Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login, e-mail address; computer and connection information such as browser type which may be aggregated with other information for analytic purposes.  
Some of our web pages, promotional e-mail messages, and/or newsletters may contain electronic images known as web beacons, which are also called single-pixel gifs. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information, but they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about the usage of our web sites and to track the number of users who have opened and acted up our promotional e-mail messages. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides. 

  VI. WHAT ABOUT THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS?

Some of the banner ads displayed in our web sites are provided by third parties. These ads contain cookies and may also contain web beacons. Cookies or web beacons received with banner ads are collected by our advertisers and we do not have access to this information. We use third parties to serve some of the advertisements that are placed within our sites and they may use information (not including personally identifiable information) about your visits to our sites and other sites to assist in serving advertisements to you. These companies may employ cookies, web beacons, and action tags to measure advertising effectiveness. They may share anonymous information with their clients such as date/time of the banner ad shown, the specific ad shown, the IP address, etc. Google is our primary third party ad server. If you would like to know more about their information gathering practices and "opt-out" procedures, please see [http://www.google.com](http://www.google.com/). 

  VII. HOW CAN YOU CONTROL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We believe that choice in how and when you are contacted is key to customer satisfaction, so we offer several ways for you to update your contact information, change your preferences, or opt out of receiving future communications.   
1\. If you have an online account, you may be able to log on and update or change your contact or account information. Check the site for further information.

2\. You may be able to log on and update or change your contact or account information by contacting us at [editor@computeraudiophile.com](mailto:editor@computeraudiophile.com).

3\. You may unsubscribe to any of our comment subscriptions by following the unsubscribe instructions in the body of any e-mail message.

  VIII. SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt important information, such as your credit card data, in an effort to prevent unauthorized access during transmission of your orders over the Internet. We incorporate standard industry practices suitable to the degree of sensitivity of the information involved to maintain the security of your personal information and to avoid its disclosure except as described in this Statement. Your personal information may also be protected by the password you created when you registered at our website where this feature is offered. The confidentiality of any password is yours to protect. You may change it anytime by following the instructions at the website where you registered. Although we use our best efforts to assure that your data remains secure when maintained by us, security during Internet transmissions or within any system cannot be assured. Audiophile Style, LLC employees are made aware of its privacy practices through periodic communications and training. We limit access to personal data only to those Audiophile Style, LLC employees or agents with a specific need to access or retrieve this information. We store data in controlled, secure environments. Remember, however, that we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information, and we are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of any third party. 

  IX. CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

Our web site is intended for adults. Audiophile Style, LLC is strongly committed to protecting the safety and privacy of children who visit our Web sites. We do not knowingly collect personal information online from children under 13. Our site includes, bulletin boards and other features that we believe are unsuitable for children under 13 and which are not necessarily monitored. We encourage all parents to talk to their kids about online safety and to monitor their children's use of the Internet. 

  X. THIRD PARTIES AND LINKS

In the event that you provide personal information to any third party via our web site or any offer made available to you by Audiophile Style, LLC, you understand that Audiophile Style, LLC is not responsible for such third parties' use or misuse of your personal information. You should review the privacy and information sharing practices of such third parties. Additionally, Audiophile Style, LLC may offer links to or from web sites it controls to other sites within the Audiophile Style, LLC family as well as to sites operated by third parties. We offer links to third party sites so that you can conveniently visit our vendors and advertisers or locate other content likely to be of interest. We are not responsible for the content, practices or policies of sites operated by third parties and urge you to inquire about them before providing any personally-identifiable information. 

  XI. VISITORS AND SUBSCRIBERS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES

All matters relating to these sites are governed by the laws of the State of Minnesota in the United States. Any information you provide in subscribing to one of our publications or registering or ordering at one of our web sites will be transferred to the United States. By visiting our sites and submitting information, you authorize this transfer, processing and use. 

  XII. ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS; CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY STATEMENT

By using any of our sites and providing us with your information, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to this Privacy Statement, you should not use or access any of our sites. Additionally, this Privacy Statement incorporates all of the terms, conditions, and provisions of the Audiophile Style, LLC Terms of Use, which are posted on our site. If you do not agree with the Audiophile Style, LLC Terms of Use, you should not use or access any part of our site.  
We will occasionally update this Privacy Statement as necessary to protect our users and to comply with a changing environment. We recommend that you check the posted Privacy Statement when you visit any of our sites to be sure you are aware of and understand our current Statement. Your continued use of the respective site means you accept the updated Privacy Statement.
